Guide to the Cherríe Moraga Papers, 1970-1996
Department of Special Collections
- Series IX. Academic Work
  - Teaching materials: Women's Studies 560, San Francisco State University: Women Building Multicultural Alliances [1 of 2] 1986 Spring (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Teaching materials: Women's Studies 560, San Francisco State University: Women Building Multicultural Alliances [2 of 2] 1986 Spring (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Teaching materials: Feminist Studies 199, Stanford University: Writer as Healer [1 of 2] 1986 Spring (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Teaching materials: Feminist Studies 199, Stanford University: Writer as Healer [course reader] [2 of 2] 1986 Spring (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Course evaluations 1986 -1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Teaching materials: Chicano Studies 1A / 1B, University of California, Berkeley: Reading amd Composition [1 of 9] 1986 -1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Teaching materials: Chicano Studies 1A / 1B, University of California, Berkeley: Reading amd Composition [2 of 9] 1986 -1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Teaching materials: Chicano Studies 1A / 1B, University of California, Berkeley: Reading amd Composition [3 of 9] 1986 -1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Teaching materials: Chicano Studies 1A / 1B, University of California, Berkeley: Reading amd Composition [4 of 9] 1986 -1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Teaching materials: Chicano Studies 1A / 1B, University of California, Berkeley: Reading amd Composition [5 of 9] 1986 -1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Teaching materials: Chicano Studies 1A / 1B, University of California, Berkeley: Reading amd Composition [6 of 9] 1986 -1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Teaching materials: Chicano Studies 1A / 1B, University of California, Berkeley: Reading amd Composition [7 of 9] 1986 -1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Teaching materials: Chicano Studies 1A / 1B, University of California, Berkeley: Reading amd Composition [8 of 9] 1986 -1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Teaching materials: Chicano Studies 1A / 1B, University of California, Berkeley: Reading amd Composition [9 of 9] 1986 -1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Teaching materials: Chicano / Latino Teatro 1990 Spring (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Student writings: Chicano / Latino Teatro [1 of 3] 1990 Spring (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Student writings: Chicano / Latino Teatro [2 of 3] 1990 Spring (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Student writings: Chicano / Latino Teatro [3 of 3] 1990 Spring (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Student writings: Chicano Studies 149, "Red Hot Brown Funk," student journal c. 1990 Dec. 6 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Teaching materials: Immigrant women's project at Brava! 1991 Oct. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Teaching materials: Creative writing workshop for Brava! and DramaDIVAS 1991 [?] Jan. 22 -Dec. 18 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Teaching materials: DramaDIVAS at Brava! 1992 June 30 -1995 June 30 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Teaching materials: DramaDIVAS at Brava! [workshops], miscellaneous promotional materials n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Indigena as Scribe: workshop syllabus 1992 Sept. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Indigena as Scribe: workshop calendar and related student writings 1992 Sept. 22 -Dec. 15 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Indigena as Scribe: writing excercises for Winter 1993 1993 Jan. -May (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Indigena as Scribe: promotional materials for readings 1993 Mar. 28 -June 1 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Indigena as Scribe: calls for papers, publishing venues, etc. 1993 Sept. 30 -1994 Dec. 12 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Indigena as Scribe: class list and biographies Fall 1994 1994 Jan. -n.d. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Indigena as Scribe: student writings and line drawings 1994 Jan. -Nov. 8 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Indigena as Scribe: writing excercises for Winter 1994 1994 Feb. 8 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Indigena as Scribe: Cherríe Moraga's journal for Winter & Spring 1994 1994 Feb. 8 -May (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Indigena as Scribe: reading list for Summer 1994 1994 Summer (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Indigena as Scribe: calendar for Fall 1994 1994 Fall (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Indigena as Scribe: fundraising letter to students for Brava! 1994 Oct. 19 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Indigena as Scribe: calendar for Fall & Winter 1994 - 1995 1994 Nov. 2 -1995 Feb. 8 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Indigena as Scribe: information on writing contest "From margin to center" c. 1994 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Indigena as Scribe: miscellaneous teaching materials n.d. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Indigena as Scribe: intensive Journal workbook n.d. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Teaching materials: creative writing courses n.d. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Articles: Camus, Albert. "Absurd Freedom" n.d. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Articles: Ionesco, Eugene. "The world of Ionesco" n.d. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Articles: Spanos, William V. :Abraham, Sisyphus, and the furies: some introductory notes on existentialism" n.d. (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Series X. Collector's Publications
  - Adame, Leonard, et al. Entrance: Four Chicano Poets. Greenfield Center, NY: The Greenfield Review Press 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alarcón, Francisco X. Tattoos. Moraga, CA: Eucalyptus Press 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allison, Dorothy. Bastard out of Carolina. Dutton [uncorrected proofs] 1992 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Arieto.--Vol. 9, no. 36 (1984) 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Azalea.--Vol. 3, no. 3 (1980 Fall) 1980 Fall (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Azalea.--Vol. 4, no. 2 (1981) 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Azalea.--Vol. 4, no. 3 (1982) [includes: "My birthings cause little commotion," p. 5 & "An open invitation to a meal," p. 14] 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ballan, Dorothy. Feminism and Marxism. World View Publishers 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Between our selves: women of color newspaper.--Vol. 1, no. 2 (1985 Spring - Summer) 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Black Scholar: Journal of Black Studies and Research.--Vol. 10, nos. 8-9 (1979 May - June) 1979 May -June (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Book catalogues: Alice B's bookservice, Berkeley. -- Catalogue 1 n.d. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Book catalogues: Turtle Grandmother Books n.d. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Boston Women's Health Book Collective. Our bodies, ourselves: a book by and for women, by the Boston Women's Health Book Collective. [2d ed., completely rev. and expanded]. New York, Simon and Schuster [1979] 383 p. illus. 29 cm. 1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bridge: an Asian American perspective.--Vol. 6, no. 4 (1978 Winter) 1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Bridge: an Asian American perspective.--Vol. 7, no. 1 (1979 Spring - Summer) 1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Brinson-Pineda, Barbara. Nocturno. Berkeley: University of California Press 1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Cadden, Wendy. Drawing Strength: Images of Women. s.l.: s.n. 1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - California Rural Legal Assistance Annual Report 1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Callboard.--Vol. 17, no. 6 (1992 June) [includes: scenes from "Heroes and Saints," pp. 10-11] 1992 June (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Calyx.--Vol. 4, no. 2 (1979) 1979 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Castillo, Ana. The Invitation. Drawings by Marina Gutierrez. s.l.: author 1979 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Castillo, Ana. The Invitation. Oakland: Max Press 1986 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Castillo, Ana. Otro Canto. Chicago: Alternativo Publications 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cat's Eye.--No. 1 (1980 Fall) 1980 Fall (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Chispas.-- Vol. 17, no. 1 (1988) 1988 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Chrysalis.-- No. 10 (1978) 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Chrysalis.-- No. 2 (1977) 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Chrysalis.-- No. 4 (1977) 1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Chrysalis.-- No. 6 (1978) 1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Chrysalis.-- No. 8 (1978) 1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Chrystos. "Before the land & water open," s.l.: Press Gang Printers [broadside] 1991 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Civil Rights Digest.-- Vol. 6, no. 3 (1974 Spring) 1974 Spring (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Codices.-- No. 1 (1985) 1985 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Codices.-- No. 3 (1986 Apr.) 1986 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Colon, Alice, 1950-. Participacion de la mujer en la historia de Puerto Rico: las primeras decadas del siglo veinte. [New Brunswick, N.J.]: Rutgers, the State University of New Jersey, Campus at New Brunswick, [1986] 66 p.: ill.; 28 cm. "Trabajaron en la investigacion y preparacion de este folleto: Alice Colon, Margarita Mergel, Nilsa Torres"--3rd prelim. p. Includes bibliographical references (p. 63-66). 1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Combahee River Collective Statement [3 copies] 1977 Apr. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Common Lives / Lesbian Lives.-- No. 1 (1981 Fall) 1981 Fall (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Conditions.-- Nos. 11 & 12 (1985) 1985 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Conditions.-- Vol. 1, no. 1 (1977) 1977 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Conditions.-- Vol. 1, no. 2 (1977 Oct.) 1977 Oct. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Conditions.-- Vol. 1, no. 3 (1978 Spring) 1978 Spring (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Conditions.-- Vol. 2, no. 1 (1979 Winter) 1979 Winter (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Conditions.-- Vol. 2, no. 2 (1979) 1979 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Conditions.-- Vol. 2, no. 3 (1980 Summer) 1980 Summer (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Conditions.-- Vol. 3, no. 1 (1981 Spring) [includes: "Anatomy Lessons"; "For the color of my mother" pp. 88-90; and a review of "Top ranking: a collection of articles on racism and classism in the Lesbian community," edited by Joan Gibbs and Sara Bennett, pp. 140-144] 1981 Spring (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Conditions.-- Vol. 3, no. 2 (1982 Spring) [includes: "It got her over" pp. 72-75] 1982 Spring (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Conditions.-- Vol. 3, no. 3 (1983 Spring) 1983 Spring (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Conditions.-- Vol. 3, no. 4 (1984) 1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Conditions.--Nos. 11 & 12 (1985) 1985 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Connexions: an international women's quarterly.-- No. 2 (1981 Fall) 1981 Fall (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Connexions: an international women's quarterly.-- No. 8 (1983 Spring) 1983 Spring (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Connexions: an international women's quarterly.-- No. 9 (1983 Summer) 1983 Summer (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Contact II: a bimonthly poetry review.-- Vol. 5, nos. 24-25 (1982 Winter - Spring) 1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Cotera, Martha P. Diosa y Hembra. Austin: Information Systems Development 1976 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cotera, Martha P. The Chicana Feminist. Austin: Information Systems Development 1977 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Davis, Angela. "The Black Woman's role in the community of slaves," Black Scholar. (1971 Dec.) 1971 Dec. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - De Colores: journal of emerging Raza philosophies.-- Vol. 3, no. 3 (1977) 1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - de Hoyos, Angela. Arise, Chicano! & other poems. San Antonio: M & A Editions 1984 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - de Hoyos, Angela. Chicano poems: For the barrio. San Antonio: M & A Editions` 1977 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - El Manifiesto y las Orientaciones Nuevas para la Diversificación de la Academia de Todos Unidos [New Directions for the Diversification of Academia], University of Texas n.d. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Fem.-- Vol. 4, no. 13 (1980 Mar. - Apr.) 1980 Mar. -Apr. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Fem.-- Vol. 4, no. 14 (1980 May - June) 1980 May -June (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Fem.--No. 35 (1984 Aug. - Sept.) 1984 Aug. -Sept. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Fem.-- Vol. 8, no. 37 (1984 Dec. - 1985 Jan.) 1984 Dec. -1985 Jan. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Fem.-- Vol. 8, no. 40 (1985 June - July) 1985 June -July (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Feminary.-- Vol. 10, no. 1 (1979) 1979 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Feminary.-- Vol. 11, no. 3 (1981) 1981 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Feminary.-- Vol. 12, no. 1 (1982) 1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Feminist revolution / [by] Redstockings of the Women's Liberation Movement. An abridged ed. with additional writings. New York: Random House, 1978, c1975. 224 p.: ill.; 29 cm. 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Frontiers: a journal of women studies.-- Vol. 5, no. 2 (1980 Summer) 1980 Summer (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Gay Community News.-- Vol. 8, no. 43 (1981 May 23) [includes: "'Mothers' and 'Daughters' share poetry," pp. 14, 16] 1981 May 23 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Gibbs, Joan & Sara Bennett. Top Ranking. New York: Come! Unity Press 1980 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Goldfarb, Lyn. Separated & Unequal: discrimination against women workers after World War II. Silver Spring, MD: Women's Work Project 1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Gordon, Linda & Allen Hunter. "Sex, family, and the new right: anti-feminism as a political force," [a reprint from Radical America (1977 Nov. - 1978 Feb.)] Somerville, MA: New England Free Press 1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Guardian Women's Day Supplement.-- (1982 Spring) 1982 Spring (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Heresies: a feminist publication on art and politics.-- No. 1 (1977 Jan.) 1977 Jan. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Heresies: a feminist publication on art and politics.-- No. 3 (1977 Fall) 1977 Fall (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Heresies: a feminist publication on art and politics.-- No. 8 (1979) 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Heresies: a feminist publication on art and politics.-- No. 9 (1980) 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Heresies: a feminist publication on art and politics.-- No. 15 (1982) 1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Hernandez, Inéz. Con Razon Córazon. San Antonio: M & A Editions 1987 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - IKON.-- 2nd series, no. 1 (1982 Fall - 1983 Winter) 1982 -1983 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - IKON.-- 2nd series, no. 3 (1984 Spring - Summer) 1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Imagine: international Chicano Poetry Journal.-- Vol. 1, no. 1 (1984 Summer) 1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Imagine: international Chicano Poetry Journal.-- Vol. 1, no. 2 (1984 Winter) 1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Indigenous woman.-- Vol. 1, no. 1 (1991 Spring) 1991 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Juan Rulfo. México, D.F.: Instituto Nacional Indigenista, 1986. 88 p.: ill.; 28 cm. (México indígena: número extraordinario 1986.) 1986 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - THE LADDER: A Lesbian Review. Vol. 10, no. 9 (1966 June) 1966 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Lauren, Jilly. Nanny. s.l.: s.n. 1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Lesbian Herstory Archives News.-- No. 7 (1981 Dec.) 1981 Dec. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - THE LESBIAN READER: an Amazon Quarterly Anthology. ed. Gina Covina & Laurel Galana, Oakland, Amazon Press. (1975) 1975 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - LeSueur, Meridel. Worker Writers. Minneapolis: West End Press 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - El Manifesto y Las Orientaciones Nuevas para la Diversification de la Academia de Todos Unidos, University of Texas, 1978 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - McDaniel, Judith. Reconstituting the world: the poetry of Adrienne Rich. Argyle, NY: Spinsters, Ink. 1978 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - ¡Mira! -- 1984 1984 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Morejón, Nancy. Grenada Notebook (Cuaderno de Granada). New York: Círculo de Cultera Cubana 1984 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Mosaic. -- 1984 Spring 1984 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Mother Jones. -- Vol. 5, no. 10 (1980 Dec.) 1980 Dec. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mujeres en Marcha. Chicanas in the 80s: unsettled issues. Berkeley: Chicano Studies Library Publication, University of California 1983 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Nava, Julian, 1927-. Mexican Americans; past, present, and future. [New York] American Book Co. [c1969]. viii, 120 p. illus., maps, ports. 26 cm. 1969 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - New Women's Times. -- Vol. 5, no. 9 (1979 Apr. 27 - May 10) 1979 Apr. 27 -May 10 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Off our backs. -- Vol. 9, no. 6 (1979 June.) 1979 June (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Off our backs. -- Vol. 9, no. 10 (1979 Nov.) 1979 Nov (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Off our backs. -- Vol. 10, no. 1 (1980 Feb.) 1980 Jan. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Off our backs. -- Vol. 10, no. 2 (1980 Feb.) 1980 Feb. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Off our backs. -- Vol. 12, no. 2 (1982 Feb.) 1982 Feb. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Off our backs. -- Vol. 12, no. 3 (1982 Mar.) 1982 Mar. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Off our backs. -- Vol. 12, no. 6 (1982 June) 1982 June (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Off our backs. -- Vol. 14 (1984 Aug. - Sept.): 17-24 1984 Aug. -Sept. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Peña, Arturo. Nuestra América frente al V centenario: Emancipición e identidad de América Latina (1492-1992). Mexico: Joaquin Mortiz / Planeta 1989 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Plexus. -- Vol. 7, no. 7 (1980 Sept.) [2 copies] 1980 Sept. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Poetry Flash. -- No. 195 (1989 June) ["indludes Cariaga, Catalina. "The poetics of Chisme"] 1989 June (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Poppy. -- Vol. 7 (1985 Feb. - 1986 May) 1985 Feb. -1986 May (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Portillo, Cristina, Graciela Rios, Martha Rodriguez. Bibliography of writings on la Mujer. Berkeley: Chicano Studies Library Publication, University of California 1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Prisma. -- 1979 Spring 1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Prisma. -- Vol. 2 (1980 Winter) 1980 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Quest: a feminist quarterly. -- Vol. 2, no. 1 (1975 Summer) 1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Quest: a feminist quarterly. -- Vol. 2, no. 2 (1975 Fall) 1975 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Quest: a feminist quarterly. -- Vol. 5, no. 1 (1979 Summer) 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Radical America. -- Vol. 13, no. 6 (1979 Nov. - Dec.) 1979 Nov. -Dec. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Ramos, Luis Arturo. Angela de Hoyos: A Critical Look. s.l.: Pajarilo Publications 1977 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - rara avis. -- Vol. 1, no. 1 (1978 Feb.) 1978 Feb. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - rara avis. -- Vol. 1, no. 3 (1978 Dec.) 1978 Dec. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - rara avis. -- no. 5 (1981 Summer/Fall) 1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Revolutionary Communist Party USA. The Chicano struggle and the struggle for Socialism. Chicago: RCP Publications 1979 Mar. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Robles, Mireya. Time, the artisan. San Antonio: M & A Editions 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Saenz, Diana. Apes in space. Los Angeles: author 1986 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Scott, Renae. Doing community outreach to Third World women. Boston: Domestic Violence Technical Assistance Project 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Sinister wisdom. -- Vol. 1, no. 1 (1976 Fall) 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Sinister wisdom. -- Vol. 1, no. 2 (1976 Fall) 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Sinister wisdom. -- No. 5 (1978 Winter) 1978 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Sinister wisdom. -- No. 9 (1979 Spring) 1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Sinister wisdom. -- No. 10 (1979 Summer) 1979 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Sinister wisdom. -- No. 12 (1980 Winter) 1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Sinister wisdom. -- No. 13 (1980 Spring) 1980 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Sinister wisdom. -- No. 16 (1981) 1981 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Sinister wisdom. -- No. 17 (1981) 1981 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Sinister wisdom. -- No. 18 (1981) 1981 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Socialist Review. -- Vol. 9, no. 3 (1979 May - June) 1979 May -June (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Socialist Review. -- Vol. 11, no. 4 (1981 July - Aug.) 1981 July -Aug. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Southern Exposure. -- Vol. 4, no. 4 (1977 Winter) 1977 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Southern Exposure. -- Vol. 8, no. 2 (1980 Summer) 1980 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Southern Exposure. -- Vol. 9, no. 2 (1981 Summer) 1981 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Southern Exposure. -- Vol. 9, no. 3 (1981 Fall) 1981 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Southern Exposure. -- Vol. 9, no. 4 (1981 Winter) 1981 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Southern Exposure. -- Vol. 10, no. 2 (1982 Mar. - Apr.) 1982 Mar. -Apr. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Southwest tales: a contemporary collection / edited by Alurista and Xelina Rojas-Urista. Colorado Springs, CO: Maize Press, c1986. xi, 158 p.; 23 cm. 1986 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Spare rib. -- Issue 101 (1980 Dec.) 1980 Dec. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Steffan, Heinz Dieterich. 1492-1992 La interminable conquista: Emancipición e identidad de América Latina (1492-1992). Mexico: Joaquin Mortiz / Planeta 1990 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Taylor, Valerie. Love image. Bates City, MO: The Naiad Press, Inc. 1977 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Thirteenth Moon.--Vol. 8, nos. 1-2 (1984) 1984 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Voices from Nicaragua. -- Vol. 1, nos. 2-3 (1983) 1983 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - West End: A Magazine of Poetry and Politics. -- Vol. 4, no. 3 (1977 Winter-Spring) 1977 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Wild Iris: a feminist journal. -- Issue 4 (1977) 1977 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Wishing Well. -- Vol. 7, no. 2 (1981 May) 1981 May (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Women's Liberation Discussion Bulletin. -- No. 3 (1981 Aug.) 1981 Aug. (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Series XI. Publicity
  - The Bridge Called My Back n.d. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Circle in the Dirt n.d. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Coatlicue's Call 1990 Oct. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Giving up the Ghost [1 of 2] 1984 -1989 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Giving up the Ghost [2 of 2] 1984 -1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Heroes and Saints 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Heroes and Saints: Tonantzin.--Vol. 8, no. 3 [announcement of play, p. 13] 1992 Nov. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Hungry Woman: a Mexican Medea c. 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - The Last Generation n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Literary events [1 of 2] 1980s (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Literary events [2 of 2] 1980s (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Literary events [1 of 2] 1990s (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Literary events [2 of 2] 1990s (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Literary events [1 of 2] 1990 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Literary events [2 of 2] 1990 -1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Loving in the war years 1984 -1986 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous clippings and articles on Moraga c. 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Moraga biographical statements n.d. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Moraga résumés 1991 -1994; n.d. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - PEN West Literary Awards [Heroes and Saints] 1993 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Shadow of a Man 1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Watsonville 1993 -1996 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Series XII. Electronic Media
  - Subseries a. Audiocassettes
    - "De Boca en Boca," Poetry by Chicanas. Produced by Cindy Madrón. 1983 June (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - "This Bridge Called My Back," [1 of 2] Reading at La Peña, Berkeley 1981 Nov. 21 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - "This Bridge Called My Back," [2 of 2] Reading at La Peña, Berkeley 1981 Nov. 21 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - "This Bridge Called My Back," Reading in Washington, D.C. 1982 Feb. 5 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Cinco de Mayo Special, KPFA - Berkeley. Produced by Cindy Madrón. 1984 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - A Class Anaylsis on Racism. n.d. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Cuentos: Stories by Latinas, + Intro. Talk [1 of 2] Alma Gorry, Cherríe Moraga, Maríana Romo- Cormona 1983 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Cuentos: Stories by Latinas, + Intro. Talk [2 of 2] Alma Gorry, Cherríe Moraga, Maríana Romo- Cormona 1983 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - "Extranjera" - songs n.d. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - "Giving Up the Ghost," "At the Foot of the Mountain," 1984 June 24 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - "Giving Up the Ghost," "At the Foot of the Mountain," excerpts, poetry: "En Route Para L.A.," etc. n.d. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - "Giving Up the Ghost," at S.F. State 1987 Apr. 6 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - "Giving Up the Ghost," from NPR's Morning Edition. Valerie J. Fisher, 206-784-9444 1987 Apr. 8 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - "Giving Up the Ghost," music. 1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - "Heart of the Earth: A Popul Vuh Story." Glen Velez excerpts, from INTAR 93 W.S. 1993 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - "Heroes and Saints," KQED-FM, San Francisco. NPR's "Living on Earth" 1992 Apr. 24, and May 29 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Humanities at Iowa - Ray Heffner w/ Cherríe Moraga & Janet Winston. "Teaching, Texts & Diversity" 1992 Mar. 8 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - "Loving in the War Years," KPFA. Produced by Cindy Madrón. 1984 July 7 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Mexicana Medea [1 of 3] BRAVA reading 1994 Feb. 21 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Mexicana Medea [2 of 3] BRAVA reading 1994 Feb. 21 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Mexicana Medea [3 of 3] BRAVA reading 1994 Feb. 21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - "The Mixquihuala Letters" lecture and discussion - Sonoma State 1988 May 9 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - "Mixquiahuala Letters" lecture n.d. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - MLA Speech 1982 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Cherríe Moraga Interview on KIQI 1990 Nov. 16 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Dub of Cherríe Moraga Interview - by Sylvia Mullaly Aguirre for: Coming From America 1991 Mar. 14 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Cherríe Moraga & Osa Hidalgo, "Reunion" [1 of 2] 1991 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Cherríe Moraga and Osa Hidalgo "Entrevista" [2 of 2] 1991 June 18 (Box 1, Folder 28)